[
  {
    "Question": "When Honeywell Founded",
    "answer": ["1905", "1990", "1885", "2000"],
    "type": "obj"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is the boiling temperature of petrol?",
    "answer": ["40-120 째C", "120-180 째C", "180-250 째C", "250-320 째C"],
    "type": "obj"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Unit of Density ",
    "answer": ["Kg/m3", "Kg/m2"],
    "type": "obj"
  },
  {
    "Question": "MSC-L stands for",
    "answer": "Multistream Controller for Loading ",
    "type": "one"
  },
  {
    "Question": "ANPR stands for",
    "answer": "Automatic Number plate recognition ",
    "type": "one"
  },
  {
    "Question": "ANPR stands for",
    "answer": "Automatic Number plate recognition ",
    "type": "one"
  },
  {
    "Question": "ChatGPT stands for",
    "answer": "Chat Generative Pre-Trained Transformer",
    "type": "one"
  },
  {
    "Question": "TFMS stands for",
    "answer": "Tank Farm Management System",
    "type": "one"
  },
  {
    "Question": "OCR stands for",
    "answer": "Optical Character Recognition",
    "type": "one"
  },
  {
    "Question": "API stands for",
    "answer": "Application programming interface",
    "type": "one"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which is not a browser",
    "answer": ["Bravo", "Thar", "Safari", "Tor"],
    "type": "obj"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is RFID",
    "answer": "Radio Frequency Identification tag",
    "type": "one"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which is not a mobile OS",
    "answer": [
      "Android (Google)",
      "iOS (Apple)",
      "Bada (Samsung)",
      "Sailfish",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "type": "obj"
  },
  {
    "Question": "It occurs once in a minute, twice in a moment, but never in an hour",
    "answer": "M",
    "type": "one"
  }
]
